[Turtle Ant] May we have your permission
to have names?
[Queen] And what is a name?
[Turtle Ant] It's like a label, my queen,
one that can be used to identify
each of us individually.
[Queen] Names, amusing little things.
The three elite Royal Guards.
I shall come up
with a name for you myself.
[opening theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[singer singing in English]
NO X GOOD X NGL
[narrator] On the hunt
for the giant Chimera Ant,
Kite's group has finally arrived
in the Mitene Union.
Now they must travel
from the Rokario Republic
to the neighboring NGL Autonomous Region.
You heading to the NGL, huh?
You know, they believe that the best way
to live is as naturally as possible.
They're pretty weird for living out there,
but you folks are even weirder
for wanting to visit them.
I don't have a clue what's going on there,
but I've already driven in
about ten big groups
just like you guys today alone.
Did you say ten?
[driver] That's right.
So if most of the other groups
are already arriving,
then we're among the last.
I'd guess they're other Pro Hunters.
You think they're all looking
for the giant insects?
Yeah. Those seasoned veterans
are really something.
That must have been hard information
for them to get.
[Ponzu] Bugs large enough
to attack humans.
Do you think they actually exist?
Well, it's pretty unbelievable, I know,
but when you stop to consider the voice
they heard over the transmitter
and what it said…
[reporter] Monsters! Gigantic bugs!
[static crackles]
It's possible it could be
some other kind of animal.
The NGL is one big nature preserve,
so it's said to be inhabited
by many organisms
that have yet to be discovered
by scientists.
It wouldn't be that strange if there were
insects that could attack humans.
Even if there aren't any giant bugs,
if we can confirm the existence
of something new, it'll all be worth it.
As a new Magical-Beast Hunter myself,
it's important that I produce results.
Now that I'm here,
I have to accomplish something.
[Peggy] According to the reports
from scouts
that went out on reconnaissance
first thing this morning,
there's a new human village
that has been discovered in Sector MA-18,
which is a region in the southwest.
There are 12 houses,
as well as an estimated
20 to 60 residents there.
Wow. That's pretty big, isn't it?
Guess there are still
a few large villages left.
I was under the distinct impression
we'd already cleaned out that area.
I shall add this one to the list.
It will be among our main targets today.
Now, Colt, can you make the trip?
Yes, of course.
Hey, Peggy, why aren't you sending me out?
Because I need you to go to the northwest
as we had originally planned, Cheetu.
Zazan, you accompany him.
But I just don't believe there are
any large villages left in the northwest.
And if there are, I bet there aren't
any strong, young humans there.
It's a lot more fun for me
when I get to chase them around!
Cheetu! We do not hunt for fun.
We are in service to the Queen.
We need only capture
the requested number of humans,
no more and no less.
Yeah, yeah, I know that already.
We'll get the job done right, Colt.
Right, Zazan?
I promise to fulfill the quota,
but I don't appreciate
you telling me how to hunt my prey.
I'll continue to do things as I please.
Cheetu's right.
It's fun to hunt humans as they run.
What did you say?
I guess that's all there is to it.
Let's go, Zazan.
Don't get too worked up, Colt.
Learn to relax every once in a while.
Makes things a whole lot easier.
Such insubordination.
Their squad is going to fall apart
at this rate.
Using names may be convenient,
at least when it comes to
leading the troops in battle,
but too much individuality
might become a serious issue.
It must be stopped
before it breaks down our command.
We simply can't allow this.
Yes, I agree.
It's important something be done.
You'll notice that Meleoron and Yunju
have yet to show themselves
at a single war council.
Hear that? Show yourself, Meleoron.
Okay, but I just want to be clear
that it isn't my fault Yunju is absent.
[Peggy] Were you hiding because
you thought you would be blamed?
You are supposed to be
a squadron leader, correct?
Now where is Yunju? Why isn't he here?
You see? It's me getting yelled at.
That's why I was hiding out.
Everything here is always my fault, right?
Well, hiding the truth
makes you complicit.
-and furthermore--
-Fine! I'll talk!
I mean, it's not like
I wanted to cover for him or anything.
He's the one who ran off
to hunt the humans by himself.
He what? In what sector?
Has a new human village been discovered?
That's not it.
You remember the humans, don't you,
the ones who fought back,
the ones who were armed with guns?
[both gasp]
[Meleoron] Yunju was
really worked up about it.
He said he was gonna go
and make them his pets.
[machine guns firing]
[panting]
[man screams in distance]
[screams]
[grunts]
[groaning]
Ah, come on.
You gotta keep moving,
or you might just get trampled.
Is that all you've got?
Come on. Entertain us more.
That's right. That's right!
[both laugh]
[Yunju] Run as if your lives depend on it!
Until you're dead.
[slurps]
[chuckles]
Well, this is it, guys,
the border of the NGL.
Those two giant trees right there
serve as both
the checkpoint and the embassy.
[sighs] Kinda makes you wonder
what's out here in the middle of nowhere.
Ah, well.
Some people are just weird, I guess.
Prepare yourselves, everyone.
The Ants are a concern, but the NGL isn't
the ecofriendly group it claims to be.
[Gon] Got it.
May I ask what brings you here?
[Kite] We're on a hunt.
A biohazard-class insect
might have infiltrated your country.
Hmm.
Well, if you're professional hunters,
I'm certain you're aware that
we cannot deny you entry into our land.
Right this way.
[Killua] Wait. You're using
computers and machines here?
[man 1] We are not technically
within the bounds of the NGL proper yet.
This area is used for diplomacy
and trading information.
I see.
Are there similar facilities within?
No, sir, not a single one.
No machines of any kind
are allowed inside the borders of the NGL.
Of course, visitors aren't allowed
to bring technology in with them either.
We're very strict about that kind of thing
which means you must remove metals,
petroleum derived materials, and the like,
anything of that nature on your person
before you can enter.
Do you mean, like, my glasses?
That's right. If your clothes,
belts, shoes, even your underwear
contain any plastic, chemicals, or metal,
you must remove them.
That isn't funny.
You want us to strip naked?
That's not necessary. All-natural clothing
is available for purchase just upstairs.
And if there are any implants
inside your body,
dental implants, for example,
made of gold, silver,
or even silicon prosthetics
that cannot be removed,
I'm sorry to say,
but you won't be allowed to enter.
You understand.
SHOP
Only the five of us are left?
I want you all to stand by
in the closest town.
We'll return here
within two weeks and contact you.
[Spinner] Roger that.
[woman] The inspection area is over there.
Of course, there's a physical exam,
as well as an interview.
Then, once those are completed,
there will also be X-rays,
ultrasound, and metal scans.
Security's rather tight.
It is,
because people have smuggled guns in
by hiding the parts inside their bodies.
We often find cameras or cell phones
in people's rectums.
Some have even trained animals
to carry laptops across the border
once they themselves were inside.
Well, it looks like all of you are clean.
Thank you all for your patience.
You may enter now, and Godspeed.
[man 2] Welcome to the NGL.
[wind blowing]
All right. Now the hunt begins.
[horses neighing]
[horses galloping]
HORSE RENTAL
12000J PER DAY
[man 1] Any sightings of giant insects?
I haven't heard of anything like that.
And even if there were any such creatures,
I doubt the citizens of this country
would make much of a fuss.
If any of us are killed
or attacked by animals,
we simply accept it
as nature taking its course, nothing more.
[horses galloping]
[Gon] Anyway, I think
we should follow along the coastline
and check out all the villages.
If we search them
and nothing unusual turns up,
then it's probably
not even in this country.
Yeah, maybe,
but that's assuming that those guys
were telling us the truth back there.
[Gon] They're still following us,
aren't they?
[Killua] Yeah.
[Killua] They say they're here
in case we meet unknown tribes
and need interpreters or intermediaries,
But they're obviously spies.
Well, I never expected
the people here to be of any help.
But my instincts are saying
it's here somewhere.
[footsteps approaching]
[panting]
[groans]
Don't move a muscle.
If you die, you can't blame me for it.
You… You're just a mere animal.
You shouldn't be bossing
a superior human around.
[Koala Ant] "Mere animal"?
I don't understand.
Why don't you explain
how you and I are different?
Shut up!
[sighs]
Good grief.
You should answer
when someone asks you something.
Or didn't your parents
ever teach you that?
[gasping]
You are hopeless, old man.
[splashing]
You can try again in your next life.
[Meleoron] Aw, man!
You killed him.
How are we supposed to keep him fresh
if you kill him?
[sighs] I can just make up
a batch of meatballs.
I'll serve them to her within the day.
Humans like that one irritate me.
They should be put in their place.
I much prefer to see them running,
terrified for their lives.
Heh. Yesterday, you shot a kid in the back
while he ran away screaming, didn't you?
If you let me handle this,
I could have secured our prey
in a much smarter fashion than this,
I promise you.
When you said, "Don't move,"
that was meant for me, wasn't it?
Giving your squad leader an order, huh?
[spits]
I wouldn't get too cocky if I were you.
You're lucky I'm such a nice guy,
so I'll let it slide this time.
If you enjoy killing so much,
you should volunteer as a feeder.
It's hopeless.
[wings fluttering]
[Colt] Damn that Yunju.
[child crying]
[Rammot] Shut up!
Quit your whining,
or I'll eat you right here and now!
-[Colt] Rammot!
-Huh?
What are you doing there?
You can't tell? I'm transporting the food.
Isn't it obvious?
Then, be more selective.
I'm tired of telling you.
The one you have is worthless.
Besides, we've already met our quota
for the day.
You're wasting your time.
[Rammot groans] Then I'll eat it myself.
[Colt] What?
Well, it's going to be eaten
sooner or later.
Put it down and walk away.
That's an order.
[snarls]
-[child crying]
-[Rammot] Hmph!
Damn it all. So much insubordination.
What?
Is there a problem?
I enjoy what I do.
You want this one?
[sighs] I guess it's dead, so you can't.
Which squadron are you from?
[Chimera Ant chitters]
-Huh?
-[Chimera Ant chitters]
I see. Zazan, huh?
She is a nasty one, isn't she?
My sympathies.
[Chimera Ant chitters]
Well, you could join Yunju's team,
couldn't you?
I hear they're allowed to kill
as many humans as they want.
If you take this as a gift,
he'll let all of you join up
on the spot.
What in the hell is this?
It's terrible.
But who could have done this?
[gasps]
[Balda] A gun?
Wait. People are fighting with guns?
[Balda] Who, and how?
Guns aren't allowed in the NGL.
[Pokkle] They're members
of the NGL underground
that manufactures DD.
[others gasps]
From the look of it,
these wounds were not made by humans.
Does that mean…
It's too soon to be sure just yet.
But if the monster we seek
was responsible,
we won't be able to handle it
with the members we have.
[brush rustling]
[Pekuba] There they are! Monsters!
[horses neighing]
[Pokkle] Ponzu! Balda! Pekuba!
Run away on my signal.
[Pokkle] Got it?
Rainbow!
Time for Red Arrow!
[wails]
Now run!
Huh?
[splash]
Completely hopeless.
[panting]
Huh?
[chittering]
[Ponzu screams]
[whimpering]
Hey, over here!
-You okay?
-Yeah.
Okay, then.
We need to contact the other Pro Hunters.
Think you can handle that?
[machine guns firing]
[gunfire in distance]
[gunfire stops]
[flesh squelching]
[Yunju] What? Is that all there is?
[Centipede Ant] No. There are more.
[bullets rattle]
Oh, my! There sure are!
I recognize the smell of living humans.
[cackles]
[laughing]
[sighs]
What now, Zaikahal?
[narrator] The Chimera Ants
continue their rampage
and have now cornered
this country's shadowy ruler.
A storm brews in the NGL,
and Gon's group,
utterly unaware of that fact,
is heading straight for its center.
[closing theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[upbeat music playing]
[Gon] Next time, Evil and Terrible.
-[moans]
-[Killua] What's wrong, Gon?
-You have a fever?
-[Gon moans]
-[Killua] What? You strained your back?
-[Gon] It's terrible.
[singer singing in Japanese]